时代华纳旗下
ACCESS 集团
华纳兄弟影业 出品
联合出品
及 沙丘娱乐
ACCESS集团
亚特拉斯娱乐 /
STONE QUARRY 出品
扎克·施奈德 影业
扎克·施奈德版
正义联盟
向女王警示
Alert the queen.
第一章
“别指望了，蝙蝠侠”
布鲁斯·韦恩
Bruce Vayne.
Bruce Wayne.
直升机因暴风雨已六天无法降落
他是从哪来的
他说他爬山过来的
不可能
有话快说
Talk.
有个陌生人从大海来到这村庄
I believe there is a stranger. Comes to this village from the sea.
在村民饥寒交迫的严冬到来
He comes in the winter when the people are hungry.
并带来渔获
He brings fish.
他乘着大潮而来
He comes on the king tide.
昨晚的大潮
That was last night.
你也亲眼看见
You have eyes, so see.
渔港结冰
Icebergs in the harbor.
四个月没有船只进港
It's four months since the last ship got through.
这个陌生人不是乘船而来
Well, this stranger doesn't come by ship.
来自远方的敌人即将来袭
There are enemies coming from far away.
我需要战士
I need warriors.
对付这个陌生人 还有像他的其他人
This stranger, others like him.
我要成立一个捍卫地球的联盟
I'm building an alliance to defend ourselves.
我必须见到这个人
It's very important that I see this man.
如果真有这个人
If this stranger exists,
他会把你的话传给他
he'll give him your message.
五千美元
$5,000 American.
我给你两万五 让我和他说话 到外面说去
Look, I'll give you $25,000 to talk to this man right now, outside.
这只狗竟敢把我们当成小孩子
How dare this dog speak to us like children.
什么来自大海的神奇人物
Ooh, magical man from the sea.
我们很穷 但并不蠢
We are poor, not stupid.
滚出去
Get out.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
办不到
Can't do that.
我们说完话我就走
I'll leave after we've spoken.
他叫你"滚出去"
He said, "Get out."
办不到
亚瑟·库瑞
Arthur Curry.
也被称为大海保护者
Also known as Protector of the Oceans.
海王
The Aquaman.
让我搞清楚
So, let me get this straight.
你打扮成蝙蝠真正的蝙蝠
You do it dressed like a bat? Like an actual bat?
我在哥谭市打拼了20年
Worked for 20 years in Gotham.
那个鸟地方
Oh, that shithole.
决战时刻 我们会需要你
When the fight comes, we'll need you.
-别指望了 蝙蝠侠 -为什么
-Don't count on it, Batman. -Why not?
我不喜欢你跑来挖我的隐私
'Cause I don't like you coming here, digging into my business
干涉我的生活 我只想独自一个人
and getting into my life. I want to be left alone.
所以你才这么做
Is that why you do this?
在这鸟不生蛋的地方帮助这些人
Why you help these people out here in the middle of nowhere?
我读过你的故事 你以为没人知道你的善行
I've read the stories. Your good deeds you think no one sees.
你会加入我们
You'll join us.
"强者是孤独的"
"Strong man is strongest alone."
没听过这句话吗
You ever heard that?
你听过超人吗
You ever hear of Superman?
他和我并肩作战时死去
He died fighting next to me.
这正是我的意思
My point exactly.
他相信团结力量大 这是我们欠他的
He believed we were stronger together. We owe it to him.
我谁也不欠
I don't owe anyone anything.
打扮成一只蝙蝠
Dressed like a bat.
你疯了 布鲁斯·韦恩
You're out of your mind, Bruce Wayne.
过去 小灰
Move over, Dusty.
克拉克·乔瑟夫·肯特
法拍屋出售
天啊 韦恩少爷 这里好冷
My God, Master Wayne, but this is cold.
也许我们可以赶上下一波牙买加的大潮
Maybe we can catch the next king tide in Jamaica?
也许斐济一 两个超人类
Might be a metahuman or two in Fiji.
哥斯达黎加天气也不错
Costa Rica's nice.
我找到他了
I found him.
他拒绝了
He said no.
你连一个新兵都没招到
So the draft stands at naught for two?
也许一个成天窝在洞穴的人
Maybe a man who broods in a cave for a living
不适合当招募者
isn't cut out to be a recruiter. Hmm?
十块钱
That's $10, please.
星球日报 每日报导星球事务
曼哈顿银行诚征建筑师
大都会警局
早安 莱恩小姐
Good morning, Miss Lane.
你好 杰瑞
Jerry, hi.
你每天都来 对吧
You don't miss a day, do you?
我喜欢这里
Like it here.
站住
Excuse me.
快上
Move!
快走 快走
Move it! Move it!
-别开枪 -快走
-No, mate, don't shoot! -Move, move!
给我过去
Get the fuck over there!
让他们靠墙站好
Line them up along the wall.
叫他们闭嘴
Keep them quiet.
-安静 -闭嘴
-Keep quiet! -Shut up! Shut up!
叫他们闭嘴
Shut them up too!
我们很快就会发表声明
We'll be making a statement shortly.
在那之前 谁敢乱来
Until then, if I see any movement,
就会害死一大堆小孩
you'll have a lot of dead kids on your hands.
要射杀他吗
Should I take him?
别开枪
Hold your fire.
里面有小孩
They've got kids in there.
他不是虚张声势 长官
Yeah, he's not bluffing, chief.
圣布丽姬中学今天有校外教学
St. Brigid's had a school trip today.
安静
Quiet!
闭嘴
Shut up!
让现代世界崩塌
Down with the modern world.
回到黑暗时代
Back to the Dark Ages.
闭嘴
Quiet!
我叫你们闭嘴
I said shut your fucking mouth.
你是谁
-Who are you?
真言套索会迫使你说实话
The Lasso of Hestia compels you to reveal the truth.
你们是什么人
Now, who are you?
我们是一群反动恐怖份子
We're a small group of reactionary terrorists
要让欧洲倒退到…
who wanna turn back the clock in Europe
-一千年前 -无聊 为何挟持人质
-a thousand years. -Boring. Why the hostages?
我们没有任何要求
We have no demands.
只是在动手之前拖延警察
We're just stalling the police while we do it.
你们想做什么
While you do what?
你太迟了 已经开始倒数计时
You're too late. The countdown's already begun.
再过几分钟 四个街区…
In a few minutes, four city blocks...
全世界都会看到
...while the world watches.
不
No!
就像屠宰场里的羔羊
Like lambs to the slaughter.
我不敢相信
I don't believe it.
相信吧
Believe it.
大家没事吧你没事吧
Is everyone all right? Are you okay?
很好 没事了
Good. It's okay.
没事了 你们可以站起来了
It's okay. It's over. You can stand up.
一切都没事
It's all good.
结束了 你还好吧
It's over now. Are you okay?
-没事吧 -很好
-You okay? -Good.
你没事吧 公主
Are you okay, princess?
我有一天能像你一样吗
Can I be like you someday?
你想成为什么样的人都可以
You can be anything you want to be.
来吧 走吧
Come on. Let's go.
今天有任何变化吗
Any changes today?
没有 女王
No, my Queen.
母盒苏醒了
The Mother Box has awoken,
但什么也没发生
yet nothing has happened.
它从始纪元…
It has slept for thousands of years
就沉睡了数千年
since the First Age.
现在为何苏醒
Why did it wake at all?
这是它出现裂缝后第一次静下来
This is the first time it's gone quiet since the crack appeared.
也许它又继续沉睡
Maybe it's going back to sleep.
邪恶永不沉睡
Evil does not sleep.
只会伺机而待
It waits.
有什么要来了
Something is coming.
准备迎敌
Prepare for battle!
亚马逊女战士 各就各位
Amazons, on your marks!
预备
Ready!
守护者
Defenders.
他们无法保护十万个世界
They have failed 100,000 worlds.
永远都会失败
They always fail.
我是来让你们见识伟大的黑暗
I've come to enlighten you to the great darkness.
我将沉浸在你们的恐惧中
I will bathe in your fear.
天堂岛的女儿
Daughters of Themyscira,
让他看到你们的恐惧
show him your fear!
我们无畏无惧
We have no fear!
召集军团
Gather the legions!
跟她去
Go with her!
你必须封住山洞
You must seal the cage!
快去
-Go!
菲莉普斯
-Phillipus!
不
No!
伊琵欧妮
Epione.
让我们光荣战死 这是对的
Honor us. It's right.
封住大门
Seal it.
拿起大锤
Ready the hammers!
快封住它
Seal it now!
用生命守护它
Guard it with your life.
-遵命 我的女王 -让它保持移动
-Yes, my Queen. -Keep it moving.
拿到了 快走
Got it! Go!
高贵的女王 你为何抗拒
Oh, noble Queen. Why do you fight?
你救不了她
You can't save her.
你救不了任何人
You can't save any of them.
伟大的黑暗即将降临
The great darkness begins.
亚马逊女战士
Amazons!
是的 我们会找到其他的
Yes, we will find the others.
拉弓
-Draw!
放箭
Loose!
他回到了他的宇宙
He's gone back to his universe.
不
No.
他去了人类的世界
He's gone to the lands of men
寻找另外两个母盒
to find the other two boxes.
我们必须点燃古老的警示烽火
We have to light the ancient warning fire.
烽火五千年未曾燃烧
The fire has not burned for 5,000 years.
人类不会知道它的意义
Men won't know what it means.
人类不会知道
Men won't.
她会知道
She will.
第二章
英雄时代
这里是有毒的
It's toxic.
很好
That's good.
去吧
Go!
跟着母盒的气味
Follow the scent of the Mother Boxes.
找到另外两个
Find the missing two.
一旦找到它们 就能形成三位一体
Once they are found, The Unity will be formed.
这个世界将加入其他世界
This world will join the others.
他会很高兴
He will be pleased.
再次看到我的价值
He will see my worth again.
有酒类专卖店那小鬼的消息吗
Anything on that kid from the liquor store?
可能有
Possibly.
"可能有"
"Possibly."
每听一次这句话
If I had a dollar for every "possibly."
就会让我更受不了你
Yeah, it would make you even more insufferable.
脸部辨识可能找到匹配
Facial scan might have got a hit on him,
搞消失的那小子
our disappearing man.
中城的巴里·艾伦先生
One Mr. Barry Allen from Central City.
也许又是误判 你得给我多点时间
Might be another false positive, you'll have to give me a little time
-才能确认 -我们没有时间了
-to confirm. -We don't have any more time.
韦恩少爷
Master Wayne,
你一直在拼命地创建这个团队
you've been working as if there's no tomorrow to build this team
但却找不到任何队友
of people you can't even find.
我找到一个 是两个 包括戴安娜
I found one. I found two, including Diana.
就因为莱克斯·卢瑟说 地球会受到攻击
Just because Lex Luthor says the planet's in danger of attack?
这跟莱克斯·卢瑟无关
This has nothing to do with Lex Luthor.
这跟他有关
It has to do with him.
我在他的坟上向他承诺
I made a promise to him on his grave.
我花了很多时间试图造成分裂
I spent a lot of time trying to divide us.
现在必须团结一心才能拯救地球
I need to bring us together and make this right.
卢瑟的警告已经过了一段时间
Well, it's been some time since Luthor's warning.
没有攻击 没有野蛮人冲进大门
No attacks. No barbarians at the gate.
也许这些野蛮人不走大门
Maybe these barbarians don't use a gate.
也许他们已经来了
Maybe they're already here.
继续找 还有什么线索
Keep looking. What else do you have?
实验室是你的了 霍华德
Lab's all yours, Howard.
11点半
今晚很早嘛 塞拉斯
Early night for you, Silas.
是啊 我提早下班
Yes, early night.
替我向你家人问好
Tell your family I said hello.
搞什么…
What the...
天啊
Jesus.
阿提密斯之箭
The Arrow of Artemis.
它将射到人类世界
It will reach the lands of men.
天空火炬
Sky torch,
英雄烽火
hero beacon,
驱散黑暗
scatter the darkness.
如昔日一般熊熊燃烧
Burn as you burned in days before.
让她看到历史曙光出现之前的黑暗
Show her the darkness before the daylight of history.
警告我女儿战争已经来临
Warn my daughter that war has come
并且保护她
and protect her.
回到我身边 戴安娜
Return to me, Diana.
你这周末做什么了 戴安娜
What did you do this weekend, Diana?
没做什么特别的
Nothing very interesting.
你每次都这么说
That's all you ever tell us.
没办法 我的生活很无趣
What can I do? I'm not that exciting.
你一走出去就好像消失一样
You might as well disappear when you walk out of here.
又来了
Again?
-什么事 -又怎么了
-What is it? -Now what?
预算缩减 盗墓者
Budget cuts, tomb raiders.
现在又加了一条"纵火者"
Now add to the list "arson."
记者在克里特岛连线报导
Yes, good morning From the isle of Crete.
我身后的大篝火熊熊燃烧
As you can see behind me, an enormous bonfire is burning.
大火燃烧了一整晚
This fire has been burning through the night.
现在已经是早上 我们至少在八公里以外
We're now into the morning and we are at least five miles away.
但还是能看到它在燃烧
And we can still see it burning as we speak.
当地居民和政府当局都感到诧异
This has baffled locals and government authorities alike
这座历史遗迹亚马逊神殿居然起火
here at this historical site of the so-called shrine of the Amazons.
-当地居民和政府当局… -敌人入侵
Now, locals and government officials are baffled as to
…不知道火势起因
-what may have caused this. -Invasion.
瑞恩
Ryan.
-你好 博士 -那个…
-Hiya, Doc. -Is the...
电子激光没有损坏
No damage to the electron-laser.
-塞拉斯·斯通博士 -是的
-Uh, Dr. Silas Stone? -Yeah.
-蔡瑞恩 -是的
-Ryan Choi? -That's us.
这是谁干的 他们有没有偷走什么
Um, who did this? Did they steal anything?
-他们偷走了一切 -那个呢
They took whatever was in here. That?
那没被偷走 对吧 斯通博士
Oh, that wasn't stolen. Was it, Dr. Stone?
对 那之前就被移走了
No. That was misplaced a while ago.
6-1-9-8-2号物件 国防部档案馆
Object 6-1-9-8-2. Department of Defense Archives.
那是什么
What was it?
我也不知道
I don't know.
你不知道
You don't know?
没错 所以我才在研究它
I don't know, which was why I was studying it.
你是什么官阶
What's your rank, Doctor?
瑞恩 麻烦你了
Ryan, would you, uh, do the honors?
-没问题 -谢了
-Sure. Okay. -Thanks.
平民
Civilian.
星辰实验室是私人承包商 我们为国防部工作
STARLABS is a private contractor. We work for the DoD.
为他们提供异常科学的建议
We advise them on xeno-science.
"异常科学"
"Xeno-science"?
外星科技
Alien technology.
比如说
For example,
超人飞船
the Superman ship.
昨晚有八个人没离开实验室
Eight people never signed out of the lab last night, Doctor.
清洁工 警卫和几名研究科学家
Cleaning staff, guards, a few of your research scientists.
他们被绑架了
They were abducted.
你确定
Are you sure?
有位目击证人 他逃过一劫
Witness saw it all. He escaped.
他正在隔离区协助绘制嫌犯肖像画
He's here in quarantine now, working on an ID sketch.
知道那会是谁或是什么东西吗
Any idea who or what that might be?
母盒在这里不安全
The box isn't safe here.
维克多
Victor,
他们闯进实验室找它
they came looking for it at the lab.
有些人被某种怪物抓走
People were taken by some kind of monster or something.
你对怪物很了解…
You know a lot about monsters,
对吧
don't you?
尤其是怎么制造它们
Especially how to make 'em.
求救…求救…
Mayday! Mayday, mayday!
船身受损 我快沉下去了
My hull is breached. I'm going down.
求救
Mayday!
有人吗
Is there anybody out there?
威士忌
Whiskey.
下次叫他要敬畏暴风雨
Tell him to respect the storm next time.
他请客
It's on him.
本应是国王的男人
King who would be man.
人类父亲和海洋女王的儿子
Son of a human father and Queen of the Seas.
我浪费了多少时间
All the time I've wasted
试图遵守我向你母亲做的承诺
trying to keep the promise I made to your mother.
说完了吗 老头
Are you finished, old man?
虽然你居无定所
You never sleep in the same place twice,
但还是一直回来这里
yet you keep coming back here.
我喜欢这里 很安静
I like it. It's quiet.
这是你继承的王国
It's your inheritance.
你应当是亚特兰蒂斯国王
You're the rightful king of Atlantis.
我们的同胞受苦受难
Our people suffer.
你的同胞
Your people.
一个卑鄙残忍 迷信无知的种族
A brutal, petty, superstitious race.
地表有什么不同吗
Is the surface any different?
没人说我是地表之王
Nobody calls me King of the Surface.
你想要什么 维科
What do you want, Vulko?
要塞附近的守卫不断消失不见
Guards near the stronghold have been disappearing.
来自天上的掠夺者
Snatchers from above.
去跟欧姆国王说啊
Talk to King Orm.
-你弟弟 -表弟
-Your brother? -Half-brother.
他想煽动和陆地人类的战争
He's trying to fan the flames of war with the surface.
他说谎
He lies.
掠夺者来自黑暗之境 他们在寻找它
The snatchers have come from the dark place. They're looking for it.
我们守护的母盒并不安全
The Mother Box our people guard is not safe.
前往亚特兰蒂斯要塞 保护母盒
Go to the stronghold of Atlantis. Protect the box.
时候到了
The time has come.
把你母亲的三叉戟拿去
Take up your mother's trident.
你不能永远弃世界而不顾 亚瑟
You can't turn your back on the world forever, Arthur.
不管是地表或海底
Above or below.
狄萨德
DeSaad.
狄萨德 我呼叫你
DeSaad! I call to thee.
荒原狼 你开始征服这世界了吗
Steppenwolf, have you begun the conquest?
这个世界是分裂的
This world is divided.
他们是原始物种
They are a primitive species.
未进化并与彼此战争
Unevolved and at war with one another.
歧见太深无法团结一心
Too separate to be one.
必须像其他的世界一样 剥夺他们的自由意志
Their free will must be ripped from them, like the other worlds.
并以服膺他的光荣信念…
Given absolution in one glorious belief,
获得赦免
to serve him.
母盒呢
The Mother Boxes?
我找到其中一个
I have found one of the three.
苏醒后呼唤我的那一个
The one that woke and called to me.
另外两个仍然沉睡
The other two still sleep,
但天启魔感应到它们
but the parademons feel their presence.
它们飞来飞去
They fly,
到处搜索 并抓走带有母盒气味的囚犯
they search, they take prisoners who carry the scent,
我则以他之名创建一座要塞
while I build a stronghold in the name of his glory.
很好
Yes.
强大的荒原狼
Mighty Steppenwolf,
你本来可以与伟大的他平起平坐
who might have sat here by the side of the great one.
但却因自大而被放逐
But undone by his self-pride.
狄萨德
DeSaad...
我跪倒在你面前
I fall before you.
让我向他求情
Let me make a plea to him
当我以他之名夺下这世界
that I may come home
能否请他让我回家
after I take this world in his name.
你背叛了他
You betrayed him.
你自己的家人
Your own family.
我看到我犯的错误
I saw my mistake.
我屠杀企图争夺他王位的人
I slaughtered those who sought his throne.
你还欠他五万个世界
You still owe the great one 50,000 more worlds.
当你还清了债
He will hear your plea
他就会聆听你的恳求
when you pay your debt.
母盒将被寻获并合而为一
The Mother Boxes will be found and united.
这里没有保护者
No protectors here.
没有绿光战警 没有氪星人
No Lanterns, no Kryptonian.
这世界将会像其他的一样沦陷
This world will fall, like all the others.
为了达克赛德
For Darkseid.
我花了几百万元安装保全系统
You know, I paid millions of dollars for this building's security.
钱花得很值得
You got your money's worth.
我几乎花了一分钟才解除
Took me almost a minute to disable it.
你好
Hi there.
新玩具
A new toy?
原型军队运输机
Prototype troop carrier.
我曾相识的一个人会很想开开看
I once knew a man who would have loved to fly it.
韦恩航天最顶尖的人才 都无法让它飞起来
The best minds at Wayne Aerospace couldn't make it fly.
但是你能
But you can?
我别无选择
I have no choice.
我需要更远的航程和更大的货舱
I need more range and I need more cargo.
我认为一场攻击即将来袭
I think there's an attack coming.
你错了 布鲁斯
Not coming, Bruce.
它已经来袭了
It's already here.
据我所知 他们来自另一个宇宙
From what I've learned, they are things from another universe.
为一个黑暗力量效忠
They serve a dark power.
一个古老的力量
An old power.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
入侵地球 征服世界
To invade. To conquer.
他们很久以前曾经来过
They came here once before, long ago.
一支庞大的舰队出现在天空
A great armada appeared in the sky,
消灭所有胆敢反抗的势力
laying waste to all who opposed it.
入侵者的首领是达克赛德
The leader of the invaders was a being called Darkseid.
这名字在每个宇宙都受到诅咒和畏惧
A name cursed and feared in every universe.
地球的守护者 和达克赛德展开一场大战
Darkseid was met in battle by Earth's defenders.
旧神族 人类
The old gods, men...
被迫迁至海底之前的亚特兰蒂斯族
Atlanteans before their descent into the sea...
遭背叛及被困禁之前的亚马逊族
Amazons before their betrayal and enslavement
以及来自星空的守护者
and guardians from the stars.
他们的历史教导他们 不能相信彼此
Their histories had taught them not to trust each other,
不能奢望创建联盟
not to hope for an alliance.
而是各自奋战
To fight apart.
当达克赛德在地球发动战争
As Darkseid waged war on Earth,
他发现一个秘密
he found a secret there.
隐藏在无垠太空的一股力量
A power hidden in the infinity of space.
他召唤暗黑秘士
He called forth mystics
他们崇拜并控制三个物体
who worshipped and controlled three objects...
母盒
the Mother Boxes.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
"母盒"
"Mother Boxes"?
坚不可摧 活生生的机器
Indestructible living machines,
使用先进无比的科技打造 看起来简直就像巫术
made from a science so advanced, it looks like sorcery.
若要征服世界 三个母盒必须同步化
To conquer, three boxes have to synchronize
合而为一后形成三位一体
and join together into The Unity.
三位一体以烈火净化星球
The Unity cleanses a planet with fire,
将它转换成另一个敌人世界
transforming it into a copy of the enemy's world.
幸存者都成为达克赛德的仆役
All who live become servants of Darkseid.
活着 但毫无生机
Alive but drained of life.
天启魔
Parademons.
亚马逊女战士
-Amazons!
冲啊
With me!
但在三位一体同步化之前
But before The Unity could synchronize,
地球的守护者组成统一阵线展开反击
the defenders of Earth attacked and fought as one.
亚马逊人和亚特兰蒂斯人并肩作战
Amazons alongside Atlanteans.
宙斯及他儿子阿瑞斯 和来自星空的守护者联手出击
Zeus and his son Ares alongside the guardians from the sky.
一群黄金时代英雄为了捍卫地球 同心协力捍卫了地球的生命
A golden Age of Heroes fighting together to defend life on Earth.
他们做到其他世界做不到的事
They did what no world had ever done.
将敌人送回星空
Sent the enemies back into the stars.
三个母盒从未合而为一
The three Mother Boxes never synchronized.
也从未形成三位一体
-The Unity never came to pass.
但在敌人撤退之时
But, in their retreat,
母盒被留在地球
the boxes were left behind on Earth.
它们的力量变弱 就像失去主人的恶犬
They grew weak. Dogs without masters
开始沉睡
falling asleep,
等待他们的回归
awaiting their return.
母盒从敌人的视野中消失
Fading from the view of the enemy,
隐匿在一兆个世界之中
anonymous among a trillion worlds.
地球的守护者立下誓言
The defenders of Earth made a vow.
人类 亚特兰蒂斯族及亚马逊族
Men, Atlanteans, and Amazons.
根据他们文化的惯例及仪式
Each would enshrine and guard one of the three sleeping Mother Boxes
各自封存并守卫 其中一个沉睡的母盒
according to the rites and rituals of their culture
以防母盒日后再次苏醒 向天启星发出信号
in case a box should ever wake again to call out to the planet Apokolips
呼唤敌人回来并企图征服
to return and conquer
达克赛德唯一落败而逃的世界
the only world Darkseid had ever lost.
有什么唤醒了我的族人守卫的母盒
Something woke the box my people guard.
它向暗黑之处呼唤
It called out to the dark place...
引来达克赛德手下的一名征服者
to one of Darkseid's conquerors.
敌人已经来袭
The enemy is here.
如果是真的 他在哪里
If he's here, where is he?
他会到处寻找另外两个母盒
He'll be searching for the other two boxes.
得到三个母盒并准备好之前 他仍在藏匿
Hiding until he has all three. Until he's ready.
我们必须准备迎敌 你 我和其他人
Then we have to be ready. You, me, the others.
他们说英雄时代不会再来临
They said the Age of Heroes would never come again.
会来的
No, it will.
必须的
It has to.
其他人 他们在哪里
The others. Where are they?
第三章
挚爱的母亲，挚爱的儿子
冷藏配送
中城
前方减速
我迟到了吗 我大迟到了
Am I late? No, I'm so late. I'm very late.
中城狗狗托儿所
你好啊 小家伙
Oh, hey, buddy. Hey.
不行
-Oh. No.
好吧 晚点见
Okay, bye. Okay.
真是拍谢
-I'm so sorry.
我迟到了
I'm late.
-你是… -我…
-Are you, uh... -I'm...
抱歉我大迟到了 不是故意的
I'm so sorry I'm so late. I didn't mean to be so late.
我是我 我来了 很抱歉迟到了
I'm me and I'm here and I'm so sorry I'm late.
因为公车没来 后来来了
Essentially, the bus didn't come, then the bus did come,
不过有个阿婆一直在找硬币
but then there was this old woman counting change for the fare,
五分 一分 五分 一分
like, nickel, penny, nickel, penny.
真是够了 让阿婆上车吧
Like, jeez Louise, let this woman on the bus.
她都107岁了
She's 107 years old,
不会再活多久了
these are some of her last few moments of life.
履历
Resume.
拜托
Come on.
那是法文来着
From the French, of course.
"履历"是过去分词…
"Resume," I believe, is a past participle of...
这可不妙
Uh, wow. That's no good.
我的口袋有什么 "有只吃纸的怪物"
It's like, what lives in my pocket, right? "Paper monster hungry." Uh...
拜托 我们应该是朋友啊
Come on. Supposed to be friends now.
好了
-Yes.
中城大学 我念刑事司法系
Central City College, I'm a criminal justice major.
你说你有遛狗的经验
You said you had experience walking dogs.
天啊 希望大家都没事
Oh, gosh, I hope everyone's okay.
瞧 照顾狗狗遇到事情 我一定会随身携带肉类零食
See, in times of crisis, for dog work, I always bring a meat snack.
能让狗狗安静下来
'Cause it makes them feel calm.
你永远不知道会发生什么事
'Cause you never know what's going to happen in this city.
我是说 天啊
I mean, oh, my gosh.
是不是星期一开工吗
Right? I start on Monday?
你一定靠近过母盒
You have been near a Mother Box.
身上有它的气味
The scent is on you.
它在哪里
Where is it?
亚特兰蒂斯族的儿女绝不会告诉你
No son or daughter of Atlantis will ever tell you.
我们的族人看守了母盒数千年
Our people have guarded the Mother Box for thousands of years.
我不会背叛自己的族人
I will never betray my own people.
你已经背叛了
You already have.
这是在地球最深的海沟拍到的
This was taken in the deepest trench on Earth.
他一定是亚特兰蒂斯人
He must be an Atlantean.
能够呼吸海水
A water-breather.
我跟他说话时他呼吸空气
He was breathing air when I talked to him.
那他就是混血儿
Mixed-blood, then.
他说他会和我们一起作战
He said he'll fight with us?
或多或少吧
More or less.
或多还是或少
More more or more less?
大概是或少吧
Probably more less.
-他说不 -没错
-He said no? -He said no.
亚特兰蒂斯人很难搞
Atlanteans can be tricky.
我的族人曾和他们打仗
My people went to war with them once.
我不确定我们能相信他
I'm not sure we can trust him.
戴安娜 如果我们要合作
Diana, if we're gonna do this,
你就得打开心房 接受我们不能…
you're gonna need to be open to more things that we didn't...
你知道的
you know...
-抱歉 没关系 -对不起 我的错
-I'm sorry. That's okay. -Sorry. My fault.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
-让我们… -难免的
-Let's... -It happens.
所以…
-so...
这是第三个人
This is the third person.
消失了1/30秒
Disappears for 1/30 of a second here.
一格的影片 看到吗
One frame of video, see?
中城的巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen. Central City.
你去找他
Go to him.
我去找第四个人
I'll work on number four.
有机与生化机械电子身体器官
Organic and biomechatronic body parts.
他是个钢骨生化人
He's a cyborg.
斯通
-预备 -就位
-Ready! -Break!
大声尖叫
Three...
eighty...
预备…上吧
set... go!
你儿子也许是美式足球校队队长
Your son may be captain of the football team
也是个天才 斯通太太
and a certified genius, Mrs. Stone...
斯通博士
Dr. Stone.
但不代表他能骇入校方系统
...but that doesn't mean he can hack into our system
窜改他同学的成绩
to change his friend's grades.
莎拉一家人今年失去了房子
Sarah's family lost their house this year.
那孩子怎么可能及格
How could that child pass her classes?
维克多是出于好心才会帮助她
Victor helped her 'cause he's got a good heart.
你又做了什么来帮助她
What did you do to help her?
哥谭市 威斯康星州
-你爸… -妈 别说了
-Your father... -Mom, Mom, don't.
他得在实验室加班
-He got held up at the lab.
他天天都加班
Okay. He always does.
他很想来的
He wanted to be here.
你老是这么说
You always say that.
妈 别再替他找借口了
Ma, you gotta stop making excuses for him.
你跟他一样忙 但还是会挪出时间
You're just as busy as he is, but you still make the time.
他只是不会表达 但是…
He just has difficulty showing it, but...
我知道他以你为傲
I know he's proud of you.
我们都是 维克多
We both are, Victor.
以你现在的成就
With everything I know you can do today,
我等不及想看到未来的你
I can't wait to see what you're gonna be tomorrow.
斯通博士 很遗憾
Dr. Stone, I'm sorry,
你太太没能活下来
your wife didn't survive.
你儿子恐怕也不会
I'm afraid your son won't either.
我不会让你死
I won't let you die.
我绝不容许
I won't allow it.
维克多
Victor.
维克多 你不必窝在这里
Victor, you're not stuck in here.
你还有大好的人生
You still have a life ahead of you.
你妈会希望你拥有那样的人生
Your mother would have wanted you to live that life.
如果你当时在的话…
If you were there,
妈就还会活着
Mom would still be alive.
好吧 听着
All right, look,
你不必给我第二次机会 但是要给自己再一次机会
you don't have to give me a second chance, but give yourself one.
如果你不想看着我
If you can't stand looking at me,
那就试着听我说
try listening.
你现在的能力 维克多
What you can do now, Victor.
超强力量只是冰山一角
Your physical strength is just the tip of the iceberg.
你拥有无穷潜力
The tip of the tip.
在一和零的数位世界 你是绝对的霸主
In the world of ones and zeroes, you are the absolute master.
没有防火墙能阻止你
No firewall can stop you.
没有你破解不了的密码
No encryption can defy you.
一切都任你摆布
We're all at your mercy, Vic.
从电厂电网到电信设备
From our power grids to our telecommunications,
每个人的生活都受到
everyone's lives are controlled
复杂的数位网络操控支配
and dominated by complex digital networks
你却能轻而易举掌控它
that will bend without effort to your will.
全世界的命运掌握在你手中
The fate of the world will literally rest in your hands.
你只要动个念头 就能发射所有的核弹
Its entire nuclear arsenal, you could launch with a thought.
全球复杂的金融体系
The world's monetary systems and its complex interactions
对你来说就像玩具一样能轻易玩弄
will seem as easy to manipulate for you as a child's plaything.
问题是…不 挑战是…
The question... No, the challenge
不去这么做
won't be doing it.
不去滥用这能力
It will be not doing.
不去监视每个人
Not seeing.
这个重责大任的沉重负担
It is the burden of this responsibility
将塑造你成为什么样的人
that will define you and who you choose to be.
许个愿
Now, make a wish.
再吹一次
One more time.
很好 像外婆挥手问好
Good job. Wave to Grandma!
你好 外婆
Hi, Grandma!
余额不足
恭喜
您赢得十万美元奖金
什么
What?
天啊 天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊 天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
维克多
Victor...
这是我身为一名科学家 做出来的推断
Victor, these are the words and deductions of a scientist.
也是我一直以来跟你说话的方式
That's how I've been speaking to you.
现在…
Now,
让我说出内心话 不是身为一个科学家
let me speak to you from my heart, not as a scientist,
而是身为一个父亲
as a father.
喂
Hey.
喂 你
Hey, you!
因为你没有发挥潜力
Because you are
一直在原地打转
holding yourself back.
你打三份没出路的工
You're going in circles, man. Holding down three dead-end jobs,
还要打第四份工 你哪来的时间
going on four. Where do you even find the time?
我会挪出时间
I make the time.
-只要再打一份工 -巴里
-I just need one more gig... -Barry.
-就能自己付学费 -你不能
...then I'm gonna pay for my own tuition. You can't.
-我说到做到 -别再折磨自己了
Like I always said I would. You cannot keep doing this to yourself.
我不想再谈这件事
Okay. I really don't wanna talk about this again.
拜托 我们有十分钟
-Please, we have 10 minutes.
这全是为了付…
-And this is all to pay
-刑事司法系的学费 -对啊
for a criminal justice degree, huh? Yeah.
为了什么
For what?
那还用问 我正在跟我爸讲话
Huh, let's see. As I talk to my father,
他因为杀死我妈坐牢 其实是被冤枉的
who's still in prison for the murder of my mother, which he didn't commit.
我怎么会对刑事司法感兴趣
Yeah, how did I get interested in criminal justice?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
真是的
Oh, boy.
我注定要选择走这条路 爸
This path has clearly chosen me, Dad.
把手给我 儿子
Give me your hand, man.
我要你听好 巴里
I want you to listen to me, Barry.
我要你听好 我是认真的
I want you to listen to me, because I mean this.
我要你放弃那一切
I want you to give all that up.
我也要你别再来看我
And I want you to stop coming to see me.
我拖累了你的人生
I am a drag on your life.
好吧
Okay. Um...
别再跟我这么说
Please don't ever say that to me again.
求求你
Please.
你知道对我来说怎样才是最好吗
Hey, you know what criminal justice would be for me?
我儿子不白白浪费生命
My son not wasting his life.
你想做什么都行 你聪明绝顶
You can be whatever you wanna be. You're brilliant, man.
你是精英中的精英
Absolute best of the best.
我不能坐在这儿 看着你在中城盲目地奔走
I can't sit here and watch you run in place in Central City
就为了一个…
for some old dude
哪儿都不能去的老头子
who's not going anywhere.
-爸 并不是这样 -时间到了
-Dad, that's not true. -It's time.
并不是这样
That's not true.
走吧 艾伦 艾伦
Let's go, Allen. Allen!
我要你创造自己的未来
I want you to make your own future.
别活在过去 创造自己的未来
You're living in the past. Make your own future.
开门
Open gate.
棒呆了
Great.
"别活在过去 创造自己的未来"
"You're living in the past. Make your own future, Barry."
可以了 开门
Clear. Close the gate.
巴里·艾伦 我是布鲁斯·韦恩
Barry Allen. Bruce Wayne.
你这么说似乎可以解释 为什么有个陌生人闯进我家
You said that like it explains why there's a total stranger in my place
摸黑坐在我第二喜欢的椅子
sitting in the dark, in my second favorite chair.
请你解释一下
Tell me about this.
这家伙长得跟我一模一样
This is a person who looks exactly like me,
但绝对不是我
but who is definitely not me.
这个人…我不认识
Somebody... I don't know.
披头散发的嬉皮
Hippie, long hair.
很帅的一个犹太青年
Very attractive Jewish boy.
谁喝牛奶啊 我才不喝牛奶
Who drinks milk, I don't drink milk.
我知道你有超能力
I know you have abilities.
只是不知道是什么
I just don't know what they are.
我的专长包括
My special skills
拉中提琴 网页设计
include viola, web design,
我也擅长手语 大猩猩手语
fluent in sign language, gorilla sign language.
硅胶石英砂材料
Silica-based sand quartz fabric.
耐磨耐热
Abrasion resistant, heat resistant.
是啊 我是冰舞竞技选手
Uh, yeah, I do competitive ice dancing.
这是用来避免 航天飞机重返大气层燃烧的材料
It's what they use on the space shuttle to prevent it from burning up on re-entry.
冰舞的竞争真的很激烈
I do very competitive ice dancing.
我不知道你是谁 不管你找的是谁
Look, man. I don't know who you are, but whoever you're looking for,
都不是我
it's not me.
你是蝙蝠侠
You're the Batman?
所以你很快
So, you're fast.
这么说感觉太平凡了
That feels like an oversimplification.
我在组织一个团队
I'm putting together a team.
寻找拥有特殊能力的人
People with special abilities.
我相信敌人即将来袭
You see, I believe enemies are coming.
你不用多说 我参一脚
Stop right there. I'm in.
真的吗
You are?
就这么简单
Just like that?
是啊
Yeah.
我需要朋友
I need friends.
太好了
Great. Great.
我能留着吗
Can I keep this?
那就像是一层三次元现实 似乎能够操控时空
It's like this layer of dimensional reality, and it seems to manipulate space-time.
我称之为神速力
I call it the Speed Force.
害我燃烧大量的卡路里
Causes me to burn a tremendous amount of calories
所以我是零食的黑洞
so I am just a black hole of snacks.
我是"零"洞
I am a snack hole.
这个特殊战斗团队有几个人
How many people are on this special fight team?
-三个 包括你 -三个
-Three, including you. -Three?
对抗什么
Against what?
上飞机再告诉你
I'll tell you on the plane.
飞机
Plane?
你的超能力是什么来着
What are your superpowers again?
我超有钱
I'm rich.
普林斯小姐 让我来
Oh, Miss Prince, let me do that.
没关系 我自己来
No, that's okay. I can do it myself.
你想要喝吗
Would you like to have some?
不 谢了
Uh, no, thank you.
你得先倒水进去
If you put the water in first.
-当然了 -才不会把茶叶烫熟
-Of course. -So we don't scald the tea.
-很好 -太好了
-Yes. -Great.
茶叶应该够多了
No, that's probably enough tea.
好吧
All right.
你确定不来一杯
Are you sure you don't wanna have some?
不 谢了 你得再让茶叶浸泡一下
I won't, thank you. And then leave it to mash.
我会的 一定会
I will. I will, definitely will.
你在打造什么
Uh... What are you working on?
这是一只手套
It's a gauntlet
布满高分子太阳能奈米电池
lined with specialized polymer solar cells.
来 让我秀给你看
-Wow. -Here, let me show you.
这是从氪星侦察舰上借来的
We borrowed this from the Kryptonian scout ship.
也许你应该…
Oh, maybe you should, uh...
-挪过去一点 谢谢 -没问题
a fraction. Thank you, thank you. Of course.
现在看看效果如何
Ah, now, let's see how that did.
好了
Ha! Yes.
还不错喔
Not to be sneezed at.
捕捉并消散能量的手套
A gauntlet that captures and dissipates energy.
这是韦恩少爷的点子
It's Master Wayne's idea.
也许你也应该打造一条套索
Maybe you should work on a lasso, too?
当然是黑色的罗
-In black, of course. -Oh.
好吧 维克多斯通
-All right. Victor Stone.
搜寻维克多·斯通
有点不对劲
Something is not working.
在这里见面 现在
看来你有个约会 普林斯小姐
Looks like you have a date, Miss Prince.
你为什么找我 戴安娜
Why are you looking for me, Diana?
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
我知道的远远超乎你想像
I know more than you can possibly imagine.
那也许你已经知道我需要你的帮助
Then maybe you already know I need your help.
全世界都需要
The world does.
去他的全世界
Fuck the world.
你很显然经历了很多
You've obviously been through a great deal.
我完全无法想像
I can't begin to imagine what.
但不管你发生什么事 现在都拥有超能力
But whatever happened to you, you have gifts now.
超能力
Gifts?
这看起来像是超能力吗
What part of this looks like a gift to you?
我们需要你 维克多
We need you, Victor.
也许你也需要我们
And maybe you need us.
我不需要任何人
I don't need anyone.
不再需要了
Not anymore.
我以前也一直这么告诉自己
I told myself the same for a long time.
我曾经失去一个深爱的人
I lost someone I loved once.
把自己封闭起来
I shut myself off from everyone.
但我得学会再次敞开心房
But I had to learn to open back up again.
老实说 我仍在努力中
The truth is, I'm still working on it.
既然你要求见我
And if you asked to meet me...
你也在努力
you're working on it, too.
挚爱的儿子
维克多·斯通 1994-2015
挚爱的母亲
爱莲诺·斯通 1973-2015
超人飞船上的金属样本被你说中了
You were right about the metal sample from the Superman ship.
我们用电子激光向它轰射X光
When we bombard it with X-rays from the electron-laser,
看看发生了什么事
look what happens.
克氏350万度
金属的内核变得过热
The inner core of the metal becomes superheated.
形成又热又密的物质
Hot, dense matter.
这是地球上最火热的东西
You're looking at the hottest thing on Earth.
跟我对毕业舞会舞伴说的话一样
Exact words I said to my prom date.
但她还是甩了我
She dumped me anyway.
是啊
Yeah.
喂 博士
Hey, Doc,
你认为蝙蝠侠和犯罪调查部 找的东西有关联吗
do you think Batman is connected to the object the CID is looking for?
6-1-9-8-2号物件
You know, 6-1-9-8-2?
不
No...
我不这么认为
I don't.
维克多
Oh, Victor.
好了 走吧
All right! Let's go!
-高登局长 -来吧
Commissioner Gordon? Come on!
给你的留言
Your messages.
不用看也知道今天是满月
Don't have to see the sky to know it's a full moon.
哥谭市一半的疯子都出来了
Half of Gotham's reality-challenged community showed up.
他们都说看到怪物飞过港口
Say they saw flying monsters by the harbor.
你是对的 老妈 金牌警校军 念牙医学院有什么不好
You were right, Ma. Police Academy. What's wrong with dental school?
"遭到飞行吸血鬼攻击"
"Attacked by a flying vampire."
"看起来像是一口尖牙的巨大蝙蝠"
"Looked like a giant bat with huge fangs."
有一个相关的线索
On a possibly related note,
实验室绑架案的嫌犯肖像素描
sketch of the suspect in the abductions at the lab across the harbor.
-看起来像… -我知道像什么
-Looks like... -I know what it looks like, Crispus.
拜托 你觉得他在这里打击犯罪20年
Come on, you think he fights criminals for 20 years here
然后跑去大都会绑架八个人
and then he goes to Metropolis and kidnaps eight people?
我今晚会找他谈谈
I'll talk to him tonight.
怎么找他
How, Jim?
你说呢
How do you think?
塞拉斯
Silas?
-天啊 -钢骨在哪里
-Oh, my goodness. -Where's the cyborg?
他叫维克多
His name is Victor.
我们见过面 说过话
We met, spoke.
给他点时间
Give him time.
你一定是巴里 我是戴安娜
You must be Barry. I'm Diana.
你好 巴里 我是戴安娜 那不太对 好极了
Hi, Barry. I'm Diana. That's not right. Great.
就只有我们
-So, this is us.
没错 就只有我们
-Yeah, this is us.
酷啊 那是蝙蝠信号 那是在…
Awesome! It's the Bat-Signal. That's your...
抱歉 那是在呼叫你
Oh, sorry. That's your signal.
意思是我们得出动了
That means we have to go now.
-对 是这意思没错 -酷毙了
-Yeah, that's what that means. -It's so cool.
湄拉指挥官 我告诉海王 外围守卫被掳走
Commander Mera, I told the king the perimeter guards were taken.
他不会派出援兵
He won't send reinforcements.
他说所有的士兵 都必须前往叛军地区支持
He says all the reserves are needed in the rebel regions.
他不但残忍而且短视
He's as shortsighted as he is cruel.
好吧 带着剩下的人马
All right, take what men we have left
在母盒周围形成方阵
and form a phalanx around the Mother Box.
你逃不了的
You can't escape.
我并不想逃
I'm not trying to.
维科跟我说你会来
Vulko told me you would come.
备受爱戴的亚特兰娜女王的长子
The firstborn of beloved Queen Atlanna.
等一下
Wait.
拜托了
Please.
我认识她
I knew her.
你至少认识她
Well, that makes one of us.
我父母死于战争
My parents died in the wars.
她收容了我
She took me in.
还真是个圣人
What a saint.
你胆敢讽刺亚特兰娜女王
You dare speak of Queen Atlanna that way?
你的女王把我丢在我父亲家门口
Your queen left me on my father's doorstep
从此把我忘得一干二净
and never gave me another thought.
你母亲是为了救你才离开
Your mother left you to save your life.
你无法想像她有多心痛
You cannot imagine how it hurt her.
她也付出惨痛代价
What it cost her.
但你现在不是脆弱的小孩
But you're not a defenseless child now.
那本是她的责任
It would have been her responsibility
跟着那怪物到陆地 然后阻止他
to follow that monster to the surface and stop him.
现在
Now,
是你的责任
it's yours.
太好了
Yes.
荒原狼
Steppenwolf,
告诉我你知道了什么
tell me what you've learned.
找到两个苏醒的母盒
Two boxes found and awake.
结合两个母盒的力量
With the combined power of the two Mother Boxes,
我完成了要塞的防御系统
I've been able to finish the stronghold's defenses.
第三个母盒在哪里
Where is the third Mother Box?
天启魔感应到它 正在寻找它
The parademons sense its presence and search for the third.
它们抓来了囚犯
They have taken prisoners
他们带有它的气味
who carry its scent.
去吧
Go.
去审问囚犯
Interrogate the prisoners.
找到第三个母盒
Find the third.
他们会乖乖告诉我
They will tell me what they know,
不然我就来硬的
or I will rip it from them.
第四章
“改造机器”
你们有多少人
How many of you are there?
还不够多
Not enough.
哥谭市各地有数十名目击者
Dozens of witnesses all over Gotham.
他们的描述符合大都会绑架案的嫌犯
Description matches the suspect in the Metropolis abductions.
天启魔
Parademons.
好吧
Okay.
天启魔一定闻到母盒的气味
The demons must have caught the scent of a Mother Box.
在实验室的那个
At the lab.
它们把人抓走 拷问母盒下落
They carried people away to find out what they know.
-那八个人可能还活着 -九个人
So the eight may still be alive. Nine.
星辰实验室的主任今晚被绑走
The head of STARLABS was taken tonight.
好吧 另一个科学家
Wow, okay. So, another scientist.
我们要怎么找到他
So, how do we find him?
附近一定有它们的巢穴
There must be a nest nearby.
我在大都会和哥谭市地图上做记号
I plotted all the sightings in Metropolis, Gotham.
看不出任何模式
No discernable pattern I can see.
地图上的路线没有交集
The lines on the map don't converge.
在陆地上没有
On land.
这是在两座城市之间的史崔克岛
These lead back to Stryker's Island, between the two cities.
这些是通风口 全都通往1929年
These are air vents. They all lead down to the tunnel
废弃的大都会工程隧道
to a Metropolis project that was abandoned in '29.
巢穴可能在那里
The nest could be there.
他要跟我们一起去吗
Uh, is he coming with us now,
因为你的车子坐不下
because we're not all gonna fit in your car.
我有更大的玩意儿
I have something bigger.
你真的觉得…
Do you really think that...
他们就这样闪人了吗
Oh, wow, they just... They really just vanish, huh?
太没礼貌了
Oh. That's rude.
星辰实验室
很接近了
We're close.
敌人的气味
The scent of the enemy.
虚无
Of absence.
黑暗
Darkness.
死亡
Death.
-我们在哪里 阿尔弗雷德 -史崔克岛
Where are we, Alfred? Stryker's Island.
你们应该就在隧道通风塔的正下方
You should be directly under the venting tower for the tunnel.
往左看 应该有一道阶梯通往机械室
Now look to your left, you'll see a staircase to the machine room.
红外线热影像显示有一群人
Thermal scan shows a cluster of people there.
就是那里
That's it.
走吧
Let's go.
好吧
Right.
有任何计划吗
Is there... Is there a plan?
你们两个
Either of you?
别单打独斗
Don't engage alone.
我们要联手出击
We do this together.
我听说过你
I heard about you.
没想到你是真的
Didn't think you were real.
有用的时候我就是真的
I'm real when it's useful.
我受够了你们的沉默 快告诉我 母盒在哪里
I grow tired of your silence. Now tell me, where is the Mother Box?
求求你 我们有家人
Please. We have families.
那你们就有弱点
Then you have weakness.
荒原狼
Steppenwolf.
好吧 我猜…那就是坏蛋
Okay, I'm guessing that's the bad guy.
猜对了
Good guess.
我现在真的超想念超人
I'm really, really missing Superman right now.
绕到另一边
Circle to the other side.
把它们团团围住展开突袭
We'll surround them and surprise him.
你接近过一个母盒
You have been near a Mother Box.
身上有它的气味
The scent is on you.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
-它在哪里 -放过他
-Where is it? -Leave him alone!
他不知道
He... He doesn't know.
等等 求求你
Wait, please, please!
你也带着气味 但是更强烈
You carry the scent, too. But stronger.
我死也不会告诉你
I will die before I tell you.
不告诉我就会死
You'll die if you don't.
不
No!
维克多
Victor.
杀了他们
Kill them both.
亚马逊女战士
Ah, Amazon.
但不像你的姐妹
But not like your sisters.
你更强大
Stronger.
亚马逊女战士
Amazon.
住手
Hold!
这一个是我的
This one will be mine.
我不属于任何人
I belong to no one.
大伙儿 这不是联手出击
Guys, this is not together.
把这些人救出去
Help get those people out of here.
我会让这些怪物跟着我
I'll make sure these things follow me.
大伙儿 快啊
Everybody, move!
再快一点
A little quicker.
-没事吧 -没事
-Are you good? -Yeah.
我会搞定 动作快点
I've got this. Keep moving.
这里
This way.
能量正在消散
The energy is dissipating.
我的手套很有用
My gauntlet worked!
晚点再庆祝 阿尔弗雷德 我需要夜蝠战机
Celebrate later, Alfred. I need the Nightcrawler.
我以为你不会开口
Thought you'd never ask.
马上赶去 启动遥控模式
Crawler's on the way. Initiating remote mode.
谢了 阿尔弗雷德
Thank you, Alfred.
不客气
Don't mention it.
惨了
No!
他们安全了 回去隧道
They're safe. Get back to the tunnel.
隧道 好 外星人 坏蛋 耍剑的女士
Tunnel. Right. Aliens, bad guy, sword lady.
轮到我
My turn.
系统全面故障
Catastrophic failure of all systems.
你没事吧 韦恩少爷
Are you all right, Master Wayne?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
你身上流着旧神族的血液
You have the blood of the old gods in you.
你没事吧
You okay?
我不确定你会来
Wasn't sure you'd come.
你是我父亲
You're my father.
快去吧
Go.
不要
No!
放轻松 阿尔弗雷德 我来接手
Relax, Alfred. I'll take it from here.
我认识你吗
Uh, do I know you?
我们在哪里的下面
What are we under, right now?
哥谭港
Gotham Harbor.
那是谁
Who is that?
快点
Come on.
戴安娜 快上来
Diana, get on!
是什么
What is it?
让我看
Show me.
它在这里
It is here.
在这个世界
On this world.
你可能感染了外星微生物 必须接受隔离
Sir, you're gonna be in quarantine for possible alien microbes.
美国政府的规定要求…
U.S. government protocols require that...
我知道规定 是我写的
I know the requirements. I wrote them.
它召唤了他
It called to him.
母盒
The Mother Box.
他抢走的那个
The one he already has.
他有两个了 他从亚特兰蒂斯抢走母盒
He has two. He took the Mother Box from Atlantis.
现在只需要人类遗失的母盒
All he needs now is the lost Box of Men.
他可能已经拿到手了
If he doesn't already have it.
他没有拿到手
He doesn't have it.
在我这里
I do.
你完成征服行动了吗
Have you finished the conquest?
还没有 狄萨德
Not yet, DeSaad.
那你为何召唤我
Then why do you summon me?
我带来消息
I bring news.
强大的达克赛德登上王位之前
Before mighty Darkseid came to the throne,
他在全宇宙搜寻终极武器
he searched the universe for the ultimate weapon.
反生命方程序
The Anti-Life Equation.
掌控多重宇宙中 所有生命与自由意志的关键
The key to controlling all life and all will throughout the multiverse.
他发现它被藏在一个原始星球上 但在他还没…
He found it hidden on a primitive planet, but before...
大家都知道你背叛了他
The story of the defiance is well-known.
我找到了那个原始星球
I have found the primitive planet.
胆敢反击的世界
The world that fought back.
就是地球
It is Earth.
反生命方程序被刻在…
The Anti-Life Equation is carved
这个世界的地表
into the surface of this very world.
你确定
Are you certain?
我看到了
I have seen it.
我亲眼看到了
I have looked with my own eyes.
主人
My lord.
荒原狼
Oh, Steppenwolf.
主人 我只是你谦卑的仆人
My lord, I am but your humble servant.
你真的找到它了
Can it be true that you have found it?
是的 霸主
I have, great one.
失落的世界就是地球
The lost world is Earth.
反生命方程序就在这里
Anti-Life is here.
你若想寻求救赎 那就找到第三个母盒
If it is redemption you seek, find the third box,
合而为一形成三位一体 当这世界化为焦土
synchronize The Unity, and when this world is scorched,
我就会来拿我的大奖
I will come for my great prize.
你会来地球
You will come to Earth?
我已经把十万个世界化为尘土
I have turned 100,000 worlds to dust
寻找反生命方程序
looking for Anti-Life.
寻找抢走我荣耀之人
Looking for those who robbed me of my glory.
我将踏着他们的骨骸 沐浴在反生命方程序的荣光中
I will stride across their bones and bask in the glow of Anti-Life.
所有的生命
And all of existence
都将是我的
shall be mine.
一定会的 主人
It shall be so, my master.
酷爆了
So cool.
从外面看 这只是一栋废弃建筑物
From the outside, it looks like this building was abandoned.
它想要飞行
It wants to fly.
你和机器说话
You talk to machines?
我和人工智能说话
I speak to intelligence.
这个说她因为软体问题不能飞
This one's saying she can't fly because of a software issue,
不过我很快就能修好
but I could fix it with a little time.
我的数据流中有个黑点
There's a dark spot in my data stream.
我能感应到另外两个母盒
I could feel the other two boxes.
我知道它们苏醒了
I know they're awake,
但是看不见它们在哪里
but I can't see where they are.
知道敌方基地在哪里才能攻击
Well, we can't attack unless we know where the base is.
就算我们知道
Even if we knew,
也没有比荒原狼更强大的生物
I've never seen a being as strong as Steppenwolf.
也许有一个
Maybe one.
超人
Hmm, Superman.
只要第三个母盒在沉睡 他们就看不到它 只能感应到它
As long as the third box is asleep, they can't see it, only sense it.
我们得不断移动才不会被发现
We need to keep moving so they can't catch up.
不 这只是延缓失败的策略 不是获胜的战略
No. That's just a strategy to lose more slowly, not to win.
难道火焰喷射器不流行了吗
Remind me, are flamethrowers not a thing?
为何不直接烧毁它
Why don't we just destroy it?
烈火也无法摧毁母盒
Fire doesn't destroy the boxes.
它们是一种未知的物质
They're an unknown form of matter.
喜欢热能 会吸收它 保存在它们的核心
Oh, they love heat. They absorb it, hold it in their cores.
你很了解这些盒子嘛
Well, you know a lot about these boxes.
非常可疑
Makes you think.
你在哪里找到母盒
Where'd you find the box, Victor?
你在怀疑我吗
Are you trying to say something?
我就是怀疑你
Oh, I'm saying it.
我们怎么知道你不是他们的奸细
How do we know you're not working for them?
说来话长
It's a long story.
你赶着要去哪儿吗
You got somewhere else to be?
纳粹在二战结束前找到母盒
The Nazis found the box at the end of the Second World War,
它被埋在一座义大利修道院底下
buried under an Italian monastery.
被送去给希特勒的路上 遭到盟军拦截
The Allies intercepted it on its way to Hitler.
1944年被带回了美国
They brought it back to the States in '44.
6-1-9-8-2号未知物件
Unknown object 6-1-9-8-2.
它被丢在五角大厦档案室七十年
It collected dust in the Pentagon archives for 70 years
直到国防部开始研究超人飞船
till DoD began to study the Superman ship.
星辰实验室的一位研究员 发现超人飞船和…
A researcher at STARLABS made a connection between the ship...
6-1-9-8-2号物件有关联
and 6-1-9-8-2.
他了解到它们都是外星科技
He understood they were both alien technologies.
不同的文明
Different civilizations,
类似的属性
similar properties.
虽然母盒已经沉睡了几千年
And though the box had slept for thousands of years,
那位研究员想出 一个可以唤醒它的理论
the researcher formulated a theory on how to awaken it.
也真的唤醒了它
And so did.
后来…
Then...
我出了车祸 本来应该死去
I had an accident that should've killed me.
但是出于绝望或是疯狂
But in an act of desperation or madness,
那位研究员驾驭了母盒的力量
the researcher harnessed the power of the Mother Box.
释放了一种他无法…
He unleashed an alien technology
完全理解的外星科技
he didn't fully understand.
他利用那股力量让我活下来
He used that power to keep me alive.
活着…
Alive...
但变成了这样
but turned into this.
母盒继续沉睡
The box went back to sleep
他也没有物归原处
and he never returned it.
那位研究员就是塞拉斯·斯通
That researcher was Silas Stone.
我的父亲
My father.
等等
Wait,
你父亲用一个母盒救了你一命
your father saved your life with one of these things?
它们不是变态杀人机器吗
Aren't they psycho murder machines?
它们是改造机器
They're change machines.
母盒没有救人或杀人…
The boxes don't think in terms of healing or killing,
活着或死亡的概念
alive or dead.
它们按照主人的意愿重新排列物质
They rearrange matter at the will of their masters,
使其再生 恢复原状
regenerate, reinstate.
恢复原状
Reinstate?
母盒拥有恢复粒子相互作用的力量
A box has the power to reinstate anterior particle relationships.
你是说任何物质的粒子 都不能被创造或毁灭
So, you mean in the way that particles of matter can't be created or destroyed,
它们的相互作用只会转变
their relations just transform.
烧掉一栋房子 粒子仍然存在
Burn down a house, the particles still exist.
房子的粒子变成灰烬的粒子
Particles of house become particles of smoke.
任何人只要有火柴 都能把一栋房子化成灰烬
Anybody with a match can turn a house to smoke.
但是一个母盒
But a Mother Box...
能够把灰烬变回一栋房子
...turns smoke back into a house.
我知道我们都在想同样的事
I know we're all thinking the same thing right now.
谁要说我才不说
Who's gonna say it? I'm not gonna say it.
谁啊
Who is it?
玛莎
Martha.
我去了星球日报 终于拿回克拉克的东西
I went to the Daily Planet to finally pick up Clark's things.
不知道为什么 现在无处可放
I don't know why, nowhere to put them now.
我失去了农场
I lost the farm.
我迟缴房贷好一阵子了
I'd been behind on the payments for a while.
老实说 那房子我一个人住太大了
Truth is, the house is too big for me to live in by myself anyway.
你知道我随时都欢迎你来住
Well, you know you're welcome to stay here any time
只要你需要的话
for as long as you need.
谢谢你 露易丝 你真好心
Thank you, Lois. That's very kind.
但我找到一个小地方 我一个人住刚好
But I've found a little place that suits me just fine,
就在餐馆旁边
right by the diner.
我不是来求助的
I'm not here for help.
我来是因为…
I'm here because
我见到派瑞先生 他跟我说…
when I saw Mr. Perry, he told me that
克拉克死后你就没去上班了
you haven't been to work since Clark died.
我办不到
I can't.
全世界都在哀悼
The whole world is mourning.
为了一个象征悲伤
Grieving over a symbol.
我走到哪儿都看到那个"S"
Everywhere I go, everywhere I look, I see that "S."
也听到人们在说什么
I hear what people say.
好像他们都认识他
They talk like they knew him.
但是他们不认识克拉克
But they didn't know Clark.
我不能拦住他们
And I can't stop them
看着他们跟他们说
and look at them
我为我儿子感到多么骄傲
and tell them how proud I am of my son.
只有你知道
You're the only one who knows.
也只有你能体会
Who feels what I do.
悲伤加上秘密的负担
Burdened by a secret on top of grief.
我大老远跑来是因为我想…
I came all this way because I wanted...
因为我想来见你
because I wanted to see you.
告诉你
Tell you...
我能体会
I understand.
我…
I...
永远都不会像爱你儿子那样爱任何人
will never love anybody the way that I love your son.
我也很想念他
And I just miss him.
我好想他啊
I miss him so much.
我也是 亲爱的
So do I, sweetheart.
玛莎 你有任何需要我都会帮忙
Martha, you know if there's anything you need, I'm here.
你可以帮我一个忙 亲爱的
There is something you can do for me, honey.
继续过活吧
Come back to the living.
这世界也需要你 露易丝
The world needs you, too, Lois.
他人都死了
The dead are dead.
母盒让维克多死而复生
The box brought Victor back.
维克多并没有死
Victor wasn't dead.
生命不是一就是零
Life is either one or zero.
不是生就是死 不能两者都是
It's to be or not to be. Not both.
你能操作母盒吗 维克多
Can you operate this box, Victor?
当然了
Of course.
但我们不够了解氪星生物学
But we don't know enough about Kryptonian biology.
谁知道会发生什么事
There's no telling what's gonna happen.
好吧 不过…
--Okay, but...
我们总得试试 对吧 我们得试试看
I mean, we have to try. Don't we? We have to try.
还有什么好顾忌的
What do we have to lose?
必须唤醒母盒才能尝试
We cannot try unless we activate the box.
它一旦苏醒
As soon as it wakes up...
敌人就会看到 然后闯进来
...the enemy sees it, comes,
完成三位一体 世界末日来临
activates The Unity. The end.
我们会把整个地球…
So, what we have to lose is the entire planet
拱手让给想灭绝人类的外星人 这真是好消息
to a bunch of genocidal aliens. That's good to know.
就算超人能回来
Even if Superman could return,
谁敢说他就能打败他们
who's to say that he could defeat them?
母盒这么说
The Mother Box did.
维克多的父亲 一年多前启动一个母盒
Victor's father activated a Mother Box
当时超人还活着
more than a year ago when Superman was still alive.
它没召唤荒原狼 没有母盒召唤他 直到…
Didn't call out to Steppenwolf. None of the boxes did. Not until...
直到超人死后
Not until Superman died.
-因为他们怕他 -没错
It's like they were afraid of him? Yes,
他们怕他
they were afraid of him.
这是唯一的办法
This is the only way.
这团队有六个人 不是五个人 没有他就没有我们
There are six, not five. There is no us without him.
第五章
国王人马
又完成了一项遗愿清单任务
Cross this one off the bucket list.
把超人从坟墓里挖出来 搞定
Exhume Superman from the grave. Check.
克拉克·乔瑟夫·肯特
你知道我们能在一奈秒内搞定 对吧
You know we could do this in a nanosecond, right?
没错
We could.
他是我的偶像
He was my hero.
好吧
All right.
亚马逊人和亚特兰蒂斯人并肩作战
An Amazon working with an Atlantean.
半亚特兰蒂斯人
Half-Atlantean.
我们的族人有几千年没说过话了
How many thousands of years since our people spoke?
不知道 我和我的族人不亲
I don't know. I'm not exactly close to mine.
我跟亚马逊人一样讨厌亚特兰蒂斯人
I hate Atlanteans as much as you Amazons do.
互相仇恨真的很没必要
Hate is useless.
是啊
Yep.
不 谢了
No, thank you.
我父亲告诉我亚特兰蒂斯有句老话
You know, my father told me there's a saying in Atlantis...
"只要从黑暗中拿回什么
"None are taken back from the darkness.
"-就一定要… -就一定要付出代价"
"Not without...Not without giving one up in return."
我们也会这么说
We say the same thing.
真没想到
How about that?
神奇女侠
Wonder Woman.
你觉得怎样 她会不会喜欢一个小鲜肉
What do you think, man? You think she'd ever go for a younger guy?
她都五千岁了 巴里
She's 5,000 years old, Barry.
每个男人都是小鲜肉
Every guy's a younger guy.
天啊
Jesus.
真是的
Oh, Christ.
该死
-Oh, bloody...
运气怎么样
Any luck?
如果你说的"运气"是指…
If by "luck" you mean
"今天能不能让它飞起来的运气"
"chance in hell we'll get it flying today,"
那就没有
then, no. No luck.
没关系
It's okay.
无所谓 我们只要把尸体
It doesn't matter. We're just gonna take the body
放进氪星飞船 它基本上是一台有机电脑
to the Kryptonian ship. It's basically an organic computer.
可以直接和母盒讲话
It can talk directly to the Mother Box.
什么 就像它跟莱克斯·卢瑟讲话
What? The way it talked to Lex Luthor?
差不多吧
Something like that.
还会出什么差错
Huh. What could possibly go wrong?
韦恩少爷
Master Wayne...
你成功了
you did it!
你组成了团队 一起打这场仗
You put the team together to fight this war.
你实现了承诺
You've fulfilled your promise.
但是想让超人死而复生 我是说…
But to try to do that... I mean...
你的罪恶感超过了理性
your guilt's overcome your reason.
再多的国王人马都办不到
Not all the king's horses nor all the king's men...
阿尔弗雷德 我这次完全凭靠信念
Alfred, for once, I'm operating strictly on faith,
而不是理性
not on reason.
但如果你开始玩弄这个母盒
But if you start playing with this little box of tricks,
可能会是一切的终结
I mean, it could be the end of everything.
你怎么知道你的团队够强大
How do you know your team's strong enough?
制伏不了冲过来的公牛
If you can't bring down the charging bull,
就不要挥舞红色披风
then don't wave the red cape at it.
是这个红色披风就可以
You do when it's this red cape.
红色披风会冲回去
This red cape charges back.
好吧
Okay.
你是对的 斯通博士 检验报告是阴性
You were right, Dr. Stone. The tests came back negative.
大家都没事 包括你在内
Everyone's clear, including you.
但为了安全起见 我们扫遍了整间实验室
Just to be on the safe side, we swept the entire facility.
谢谢你 汤玛斯 所以我可以走了吗
Well, thank you, Thomas. That means I'm free to go?
当然了
Absolutely.
-谢了 -大家听好
-Thanks. -Listen up, everyone.
你们都没事了 收拾你们的东西
You're all clear. So, gather your things.
如果需要更多医疗照顾…
If you need more medical attention...
亚瑟 我问你 哪个比较低调 选项"A"
Arthur, yes, your opinion. Less preposterous. Option "A"?
-绝对不是"A" -好吧
-Definitely not "A." -Okay.
或是…"B"
Or... "B"?
我再看看选项"Ａ"
Let me see "A" again?
好了 该换装了
Right. We should get dressed.
我一直都穿着
I'm always dressed.
识别证
ID?
ID.
遵命
Aye, aye.
"遵命"
"Aye, aye"?
星辰实验室人事档案
卫斯理·罗伊
宪兵 允许通行
可以了
Okay.
"可以" 可以了
"Okay"? Oh, gee, okay!
博士
Doc!
他们放你出来了
They let you out of quarantine.
是啊 他们终于肯听我讲道理
Yeah, I finally got them to listen to reason.
现在让我们看看电子激光
Now, let's take a look and see what progress we've made
有什么进展
with the electron-laser.
我们有了真正的进展 让我给你看
We've made some real progress. Let me show you.
维克多 清空这地方
Victor, clear this place out.
没问题
Done.
红色警戒 受到污染
Code Red. Contamination breach.
生化威胁
全体人员立刻疏散
All personnel evacuate immediately.
生化威胁红色警戒
Bio red five.
感应器侦测到外星微生物
The sensor's picking up a microbe of alien origin.
外星微生物不可能
A microbe of alien origin? That doesn't make any sense.
一定是虚惊一场
It's gotta be a false alarm.
各位 关闭实验室 尽快离开
All right, people, shut it down. Let's go.
-刚刚才扫过一遍 -走吧
-Ryan, we just had it swept. -We have to go, Doc.
-一定有人误触警报 -走吧 博士
Think about it. It's gotta be a false alarm. -Let's go, Doc.
-想想看 -全员撤离
-Think about it. Full base evacuation! Everyone out!
听好 等等 该死
Look, wait! Wait! Shit!
保持冷静 前往最近出口
Remain calm and proceed to the nearest exit.
注意 全体人员
Attention, all personnel.
快点 大家都出去 快点
Go! Go! Everybody out! Come on! Move!
快走 快啊
Move! Come on! Go, go!
大家都出去 快点
Everybody out! Go!
生化威胁
安全
搞定
Yes!
搞定了
Gotcha!
这是塞拉斯·斯通博士 收到吗
Post Commander, this is Dr. Silas Stone, do you read?
-请说 -这是假警报
-Go ahead, Dr. Stone. -This is a false alarm.
有人骇入系统 我们得…
Someone has hacked into the system. We must alert...
维克多
Victor.
斯通博士 你在吗 我没收到
Dr. Stone, you there? I don't copy.
我搞错了
I was mistaken.
警报是真的
The alarm's legit.
大家都出去 任何人 我重复
Everybody out. And nobody, I repeat,
没有我的允许 任何人都不准回来
nobody comes back inside without my say-so.
收到了
Roger that, sir.
大家都出来
Get the civilians out!
快点 快点
Let's go! Let's go!
-大家都安全出来了 -应该吧
-Everybody got out okay? -I think so.
-每一个人 -对
-Everybody? -Yes.
这里
This way.
它知道他来了
It knows he's here.
超紧张的
Ooh, that's intense.
太惊人了
This is amazing.
太疯狂了
This is crazy.
什么 现在才说疯狂
Oh, what? Now it's crazy?
你们这群疯子最好知道自己在干嘛
You two lunatics better know what you're doing.
露易丝·莱恩
星球日报记者
验孕棒
系统即将上线
Systems coming online.
欢迎 维克多 您想接手掌控吗
Welcome, Victor. Would you like to assume command?
我进去了
I'm in.
这艘飞船说母盒有敌意
The ship says the Mother Box is hostile.
我可以取消安全协定
I can override the security protocols,
但是没时间修复卢瑟对主电容器
but there's no time to repair all the electrical damage
造成的所有的电力损害
that Luthor's power surges caused to the primary capacitors.
说白话
English.
电流不够 无法唤醒母盒
There's not enough charge to wake the box.
我可能有办法
I might be able to do it.
我也许可以启动它
I mean, I might be able to jump-start it.
我不喜欢打破这规则
I don't like to break this rule,
但是当我接近光速 我…
but when I approach the speed of light, I...
听着 时间会发生疯狂的事
Look, crazy things happen to time,
但要是我成功了 就能制造巨大的电力
but if I do it, I create massive electrical power.
我可以往回跑 只要距离够远
I could backtrack, if I can get enough distance,
就能传导大量电流
I can conduct a significant electrical current.
也许可以唤醒母盒 如果…
I might be able to wake the box, if that's...
还是要这么做的话
still what we want?
没错 开始吧
It is. Do it.
你好 莱恩小姐
Hey, Miss Lane.
早安
Morning.
我以为你不会来了
I didn't think you were coming.
最后一次
One last time.
封锁线 请勿跨越
我看到发动机 这一定是终点线
I see engines, so this must be the end of the line. So I'm...
我就位了
I'm in position.
准备开始投放程序
Ready to initiate drop sequence.
母盒准备好了
The Mother Box is ready.
这艘飞船在求我不要唤醒母盒
The ship's begging me not to wake the box.
-这是无法逆转的程序 -它很害怕
This action is irreversible. It's afraid.
它知道荒原狼会来找它
It knows Steppenwolf will come for it.
我们知道了 继续吧
We know that already. Continue.
我强烈建议不要启动
I strongly advise against activation.
巴里 我要开始倒数了
Barry, I'm initiating the countdown.
这是无法逆转的程序
This action is irreversible.
-五 -五
-Five... -Five...
五
-Five...
-天启星有敌意 -馊主意
-Apokoliptian technology is hostile. -This is a bad idea.
并不是 继续吧
No, it isn't. Keep going.
四
Four...
-四 -四
-Four... -Four...
-我强烈建议不要启动 -我们得立刻中止
I strongly advise against activation. -We need to abort, now.
快动手
-Just do it.
-三 -三
-Three... -Three...
三
Three...
-二 -二
-Two... -Two...
-二 -这是无法逆转的程序
-Two... -This course is irreversible.
-一 -一
-One. -One.
-一 -这是无法逆转的程序
One. This action is irreversible.
正义联盟
-维克多 -不
-Victor? -No.
上
Go?
未来已经在现在扎根
The future has taken root in the present.
快趴下
-Get down!
你若在寻找他的纪念碑 看看你周围
他活过来了
He's back.
不太对劲 他在扫描我们
Something's wrong. He's scanning us.
什么
What?
维克多
Victor?
-该死 -你在干嘛
-Shit. -What are you doing?
是我的自动防御系统
It's my auto-defense system.
它感应到危险
It senses danger.
维克多 住手
Victor, no! Victor!
-我无法控制 -住手
-I can't control it. -Don't!
卡尔·艾尔 不要
Kal-El, no!
他头脑不清楚 不知道自己是谁
He's confused. He doesn't know who he is.
亚瑟 我们得制伏他
Arthur, we need to restrain him.
卡尔·艾尔 最后的氪星之子
Kal-El, the last Son of Krypton...
回想你是谁
remember who you are.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you...
快逃
Let's go!
你最好闪边
You should probably move.
-没事吗 -没事
-You all right? -Yeah.
起来 去找掩护 快去
Get up. Take cover back there. Go.
别逼我这么做
Please don't make me do this.
克拉克
Clark.
克拉克 不
Clark, no.
克拉克
Clark.
不
No.
这世界需要你
This world needs you.
克拉克
Clark.
别开枪
Whoa! Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
克拉克
Clark.
求求你
Please.
走吧
Just go.
没错
Yeah.
我们走吧
Let's go.
真是拍谢
I'm so sorry.
找掩护
Take cover!
-他来了 -母盒
-He's coming. -The Mother Box.
它在哪里
Where is it?
快点
Come on.
注意 实验室受到入侵
Attention, security breach detected.
第四区 第三层
Sector Four, Level Three.
立刻执行封锁程序
Implement lockdown procedures immediately.
把母盒给我
Give me the Mother Box.
不 不
No, no, no.
爸 等等 不要
Dad, wait! Don't!
末日即将开始
So begins the end.
维克多
Victor?
维克多 你没事吧 站起来
Vic... Whoa, Victor. Are you okay, man? Come on.
维克多
Victor?
他死了
He's dead.
什么
What?
我父亲
My father.
我没能救他 我没办法
I didn't save him. I couldn't.
天啊
Oh, my God.
他父亲是因我们而死
His father's dead 'cause of us.
我就说唤醒母盒是个馊主意
I told you waking that box was a bad idea.
这不是个馊主意
It wasn't a bad idea.
我们需要超人 现在仍然需要
We needed Superman. We still do.
不管是什么回来了 那不是超人
Well, whatever returned, it isn't Superman.
也许是他的躯体和超能力 但那不是他
His body and powers, maybe. But it ain't him.
那是他
It is him.
他认得露易丝·莱恩
He recognized Lois Lane.
-谁 -他挚爱的女人
-Who? -The woman he loves.
-他记得她 -才怪
-He remembers her. -Nah.
他会去找她是因为她不怕他
He went to her 'cause she wasn't afraid of him.
这叫做直觉 戴安娜
It's called instinct, Diana.
等等 荒原狼去了哪儿
Wait, where did Steppenwolf go?
他回去基地组装三个母盒
He's gone back to his base to assemble the three boxes.
我们不知道他的基地在哪里 或是还要多久…
And we don't know where his base is. -Or how long until...
几个小时
-Hours.
盒子一旦同步 形成三位一体
The boxes synchronize, Unity forms,
我们不能及时阻止他 地球就完了
we don't get there in time to stop it, the planet dies.
这不像你
This is not your...
他早就知道
He knew.
他早就知道了
He knew, he knew, he knew.
他不是想要摧毁那个母盒
He wasn't trying to destroy the box...
而是想要让它过热
he was trying to superheat it.
让核心变成核反应炉以外 地球上最热的东西
He made the core the hottest thing on Earth outside of a nuclear reactor.
-那么热的东西一定会… -热源影像系统
Now, anything that hot would have to...Blink off the charts
一定会破表
on a thermal imaging system.
你父亲为了标记母盒牺牲自己
Your father sacrificed himself to mark that box.
我们得回我的实验室使用卫星
We have to get back to my lab and use the satellite
扫描地球哪里有热异常
to scan the Earth for thermal anomalies.
我已经在扫描了
I'm already on it.
什么 你有一颗卫星
I'm sorry. You have a satellite?
我有六颗
I have six.
是喔
Right.
咱们去找那个混帐东西
Let's go find the son of a bitch.
第六章
“更黑暗的东西”
法拍屋出售
你把我带来这里
You brought us here.
你记得
You remembered.
这是我的家
This is home.
你说话了
You spoke.
我之前没有吗
Did I not before?
你母亲迟缴了房贷
Your mother got behind on the payments.
没有告诉任何人
She never told anyone.
我不明白
I don't understand.
她的自尊心很强 克拉克
She's a proud woman, Clark.
穿上去
Here.
她很喜欢这里
She loved it here.
我也是
So did I.
这太酷了
This is awesome.
我带了一些朋友来
Brought some friends.
天啊 太棒了
Oh, gosh, yes! Yes!
大伙儿 这是阿尔弗雷德 我替他工作
Everyone, this is Alfred. I work for him.
-阿尔弗雷德 -你好 女士
-Alfred. -Good day, ma'am.
这里真的很酷 阿尔弗雷德
It's badass, Alfred.
我去泡茶
Well, I'll put on the tea.
太好了
Great.
不知道哪里有这么多杯子
I don't know where we're gonna find the cups.
那就是母盒 就在那里
There's the Mother Box, right there.
显示可见光谱
Go to visible spectrum.
普扎诺夫
Pozharnov.
离莫斯科不远的鬼城
Ghost city not far from Moscow.
三十年前发生核事故后被废弃
It's been abandoned since the nuclear accident there 30 years ago.
就连军队也不进去
Not even the army goes in.
是啊 辐射性一定强到
Right, it's probably so radioactive
你的脖子会长出另一只脚
that you grow an extra foot outta your neck.
不再是这样了
Not anymore.
他收集了辐射 用来创建他的基地
He's harvested the radiation to build his base.
放大
Zoom.
他到底在盖什么
What the hell is he building?
三位一体在里面
The Unity's in there.
我们要从上面进攻
We'll attack from above.
炸药无法分开母盒
Explosives won't separate the boxes,
只会强化它们的联系
only strengthen their bond.
什么 我们不能炸掉它
What? So we can't blow it up?
不能从外面
Not from the outside.
我想插入合而为一的母盒
I want to plug into The Unity, one-on-one.
和它融为一体
Fuse with it.
从内部削弱它的连结 就能够再把它拆成三个
Weaken its bond from the inside so we can break it back into three.
不行 你不知道你会面对什么
No, you don't know what you'd be up against.
你得一个人融入三位一体
You'd have to stream into The Unity by yourself.
这三个母盒结合起来足以毁天灭地
These boxes together are world destroyers.
它们存在了十亿年
A billion years old.
绝对会钻进你脑袋 找到你的弱点
They'll get inside you and find your weaknesses
和你的恐惧 并用来摧毁你
and your fears, and use them to destroy you.
只要让我进去 替我争取时间
Just get me in and get me time.
你可能会死 维克多
You could die, Victor.
我不这样做 我们都会死
If I don't, we all die. Period.
我失去了一切
I got nothing left.
你不是要我使用这些超能力吗
You wanted me to use these gifts, right?
我就要这么做
That's what I'm gonna do.
好吧 所以…
Okay. So...
维克多想和末日母盒 合而为一拯救世界
if Victor wants to try to save the world by fusing with the doom boxes,
那就让他这么做吧
I say we put him in the doom boxes.
但要让他这么做就得攻击基地
But getting him in means attacking that base.
深入地狱向魔鬼与他的军团…
Fighting the devil and his army
正式开战
in hell.
这家伙在他摧毁的星球上
I mean, this guy's probably fought
大概打过成千上万个超级英雄 对吧
hundreds of thousands of other superbeings on the other planets he's destroyed, right?
我们得假设他都赢了
And we have to assume he's won.
我才不管他在多少个地狱 打过多少恶魔
I don't care how many demons he's fought in how many hells...
他没打过我们 团结一致的我们
he's never fought us. Not us united.
我猜你说"愿意"
Take that as a "yes."
什么
What?
那只婚戒
The ring.
你真的回来了
You're really back.
我得到第二次机会
I have a second chance, Lo.
绝对不会白白浪费
And I am not gonna waste it.
真的是你吗
Are you really you?
真的是我 妈
I'm really me, Ma.
听好 妈
Listen, Ma.
他们让我回来一定有原因
They wanted me back for a reason.
我得知道为什么
I need to find out why.
维克多怎么样
How's Victor doing?
你也知道 他想独处一下
You know, wanted to be by himself.
我们要求一个刚失去父亲的孩子…
We're asking a kid who just lost his father
对抗全宇宙最强大的机器
to go up against the most powerful machines in the universe.
这不公平
It's not fair.
我以为你不在乎
I thought you didn't care?
我从来没这么说过
I never said that.
怎么了
What is it?
我做过一个梦 不晓得 几乎就像一种预感
I had a dream, like, I don't know, almost like a premonition.
那是世界末日
It was the end of the world
巴里·艾伦就在这里
and Barry Allen was right here
他跟我说 "露易丝·莱恩才是关键"
and he said to me, "Lois Lane is the key."
对超人来说…她是
She is... to Superman.
每个人都有心爱的人
Every heart has one.
我想不只是这样
I think it's something more.
这是更黑暗的东西
Something darker.
韦恩少爷
Master Wayne.
Master Wayne!
你得来看看
You need to see this.
你修好了
You fixed it.
它想要飞行
It wanted to fly.
飞行是它的本能
Flight is its nature.
也是你的
Yours, too.
他会来的 阿尔弗雷德 我知道
He'll be here, Alfred, I know it.
你为何这么肯定
What makes you so sure?
信念 阿尔弗雷德 信念
Faith, Alfred. Faith.
终于
At last.
准备迎接他的到来
Prepare for his arrival.
我即将得到救赎
My redemption is nigh.
合而为一
Unite.
同步化
Synchronize.
卫星显示他打造了一个防御圆顶
The satellites revealed he's created a defensive dome.
这是个设计缺陷
It's a design flaw.
把塔台射倒 圆顶就会崩垮
Take out the tower, the dome will fall.
敌人不会料到我们正面攻击
The enemy never anticipated a frontal assault.
是啊 因为他没想到 有人会这么疯狂
Right, probably 'cause he didn't think anyone would be that nuts.
布鲁斯是对的
Bruce is right.
我们必须摧毁防御圆顶
We've got to destroy the defensive dome
在它们同步化之前找到母盒
so we can reach The Unity before it synchronizes.
要是圆顶没被摧毁呢
What if the dome's not destroyed?
它一定会被摧毁
It'll be destroyed.
维克多一旦融入三位一体
Once Victor is linked with The Unity
有巴里的协助 他就能突破母盒的防御
with Barry's help, he'll break through The Unity's defenses.
提醒我 我该怎么做
Remind me, how's that again?
用爱的力量
Uh, with the power of love.
-巴里 -我得造成能量大爆发
-Barry. -With a catastrophic energy surge.
很好
Good.
你得比以前跑得更快
You'll have to run faster than you've ever attempted
才能产生这么大的电流
to generate a charge of that size.
然后直接碰触维克多的身体
And then you make physical contact with Victor.
那股能量应该能让他进入母盒
That force should propel him inside The Unity.
维克多 之后就靠你了
And, Victor, it's all up to you.
在它同步化之前把它扯开
Take it apart from the inside before it synchronizes.
我们终于有了计划
Whew. We actually finally have a plan.
我们有了计划
We have a plan.
艾尔之家的标记代表希望
The symbol of the house of El means hope.
这希望包含了一个基本的信念
Embodied within that hope is the fundamental belief
那就是每个人都有行善的潜力
in the potential of every person to be a force for good.
克拉克
Clark...
那就是你能带给他们的
That's what you can bring them.
你被送来这里是有原因的
...you were sent here for a reason.
你将给地球的人类 一个努力达到的理想
You will give the people of Earth an ideal to strive towards.
就算你必须穷尽一生
And even if it takes you the rest of your life,
也得尽全力找到你来这里的原因
you owe it to yourself to find out what that reason is.
他们会犯错 也会失败
They will stumble, they will fall.
但你必须做出选择
You're gonna have to make a choice.
他们将与你一起迎向阳光
They will join you in the sun, Kal.
你必须选择是否要 骄傲地站在全人类面前
A choice of whether to stand proud in front of the human race or not.
你将帮助他们完成奇迹
You will help them accomplish wonders.
氪星所有的希望和梦想 都寄托在你身上
All the hopes and dreams of Krypton live in you now.
我真为你感到骄傲 儿子
I'm so proud of you, son.
你母亲和我都很爱你
Your mother and I loved you.
你母亲和我都知道你会改变世界
Your mother and I knew you would change the world.
你的心受到考验
Your heart was tested.
我知道这很难 克拉克
I know it's been hard, Clark.
但你给了他们的世界一个希望
But you gave hope to their world.
你必须让他们看到你是谁
You need to show them who you are.
爱他们吧 卡尔·艾尔
Love them, Kal.
就像我们爱你一样
The way we loved you.
飞吧 儿子
Fly, son.
是时候了
It's time.
我要把塔台射倒 破坏力场圆顶
I'm gonna take out that tower and knock down that shield dome.
不管你们看到什么
Whatever you see,
都要按照计划
stick to the plan.
这就是我把你们聚在一起的原因
It's why I brought you together.
布鲁斯 撤退 你不会成功的
Bruce, pull back. You're not gonna make it.
只要敲大声一点
Just have to knock a little louder.
杀了他
Kill him!
快去捍卫三位一体
Get to the carriage. Defend The Unity.
惨了
Oh, shit.
塔台倒了
The tower's down.
收到吗
Do you read me?
收到了
Uh, yeah, loud and clear.
你没事吗
Are you okay?
布鲁斯
Bruce? Bruce?
快去反应炉
Get to the reactor.
我会尽量把这些怪物引开来
I'll lure as many of these monsters away from you as I can.
那是什么意思
-What does that mean?
别担心我 快去找到母盒
Don't worry about me. Get to The Unity.
它们来了
They're here.
布鲁斯
Bruce?
失去讯号
Comm went dead.
上吧
Let's go.
跟我来呀 你们这群臭虫
Come on, follow me, you damn insects.
严重受损
Critical damage.
你真的发疯了
You really are outta your mind.
不客气
You're welcome.
厉害 兄弟
My man.
放心 我们能搞定
Yeah, we got this.
你去做该做的事
You go do your thing.
我猜你就是阿尔弗雷德
I'm assuming you're Alfred.
肯特少爷
Master Kent.
他说你会来
He said you'd come.
希望你没有来得太晚
Now, let's hope you're not too late.
喂
-Hey!
记得我吗
Remember me?
第二回合
Round two?
好啊
Hell yeah.
上吧
Shall we?
告诉我 亚马逊女战士
Tell me, Amazon,
你为何抛弃自己的姐妹
why did you abandon your own sisters
跑来跟这些卑微的生物
only to cast your lot with these creatures
混在一起
clinging to their puny lives?
你没能赶去保护她们被我屠杀
You weren't there to protect them from me.
可悲的是 你本来可以的
And, sadly, you could have.
巴里 我就位了
Barry, I'm in position.
好 我来产生电流
Okay. I built the charge.
你来倒数
You call it.
等我倒数到一
Barry, on one.
三 二…
Three, two...
放开我
Get the hell off me!
维克多
Victor!
我看着你的小岛燃烧
I watched your island burn,
你的姐妹哀求我饶她们一命
your sisters begging for their lives.
你母亲也一样
As did your mother.
骗子
Liar.
我撑不住了
I can't maintain this!
维克多
Victor!
维克多 我撑不住了
Victor, I can't hold this!
为了达克赛德
For Darkseid.
没什么用
Not impressed.
好吧
All right.
卡尔·艾尔
Kal-El.
巴里 我连上了母盒
Barry, I'm connected to The Unity.
我需要电流才能进去
I need the charge to get inside.
巴里
Barry?
巴里 你没事吧
Barry, are you okay?
巴里
Barry!
我没力了 我得喘口气
I got the wind knocked out of me. Need a few seconds, that's all!
巴里 你在哪里 它快要同步化了
Barry, where are you? It's almost synchronized!
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
喔买尬 快点愈合 巴里
Oh, my God. Gotta heal, Barry.
愈合啊
Heal. Heal.
巴里
Barry!
太迟了
It's too late.
噢 不
Oh, no.
他来了
He's here!
好吧
Okay.
我得超越光速 跑得比光速更快
Just gotta go faster than the speed of light. Far beyond the speed of light.
你得打破规则 巴里 现在就得这么做
You gotta break the rule, Barry, and you gotta do it now.
爸…
Dad...
不管发生什么事 我都要你知道
whatever happens, I want you to know
你儿子也是一个英雄 爸
your kid was one of them, Dad.
精英中的精英
One of the best of the best.
创造自己的未来
Make your own future.
也创造自己的过去
Make your own past.
一切都没事了
It's all right now.
斯通 哥谭市立大学
哥谭市
我们一直在等着你 维克多
We've been waiting for you, Victor.
我破碎的儿子
My broken boy.
你不会再孤单了
You don't have to be alone anymore.
我们会再全家团圆
We'll be together again.
我们可以像以前一样
we can put it back, Vic.
让你恢复原状
Make you whole again.
我并没有破碎
I'm not broken.
我也并不孤单
And I'm not alone.
超人
Superman!
我跟你说过
I told you
荒原狼会失败
Steppenwolf would fail.
没错 你是说过
Yes. Yes, you did.
我的主人 母盒被摧毁了
My master, now that the Mother Boxes have been destroyed,
你要怎么得到你的大奖
how will you retrieve your great prize?
找到了反生命方程序 狄萨德
Anti-Life is found, DeSaad.
我们会不择手段得到它
And we will stop at nothing to possess it.
准备出动舰队
Ready the armada.
我们要用老方法
We will use the old ways.
后记
再为人父
这又是你父亲
Your father twice over.
现在 让我说出内心话 不是身为一个科学家
Now, let me speak to you from my heart, not as a scientist,
而是身为一个父亲
as a father.
让我再为人父
Your father twice over.
我把你带到这世界 又把你带回来
I brought you into the world and back to it.
你无法想像我有多为你感到骄傲
You can't imagine how proud I am of who you are.
一直都是如此
Have always been.
我浪费了这么多年没有陪你 也犯了太多错没有改过
So many years with you I wasted. So many wrongs I've left un-righted.
一切都会崩裂 维克多
Everything breaks, Victor.
一切都会改变
Everything changes.
我得去见我父亲
I gotta go see my father.
这世界伤痕累累
The world is hurt.
支离破碎
Broken.
无法改变
Unexchangeable.
飞船是你的了 小子 你是老大
Ship's all yours now, kid. You're the boss.
"蔡瑞恩 纳米科技总监"
"Ryan Choi, Director of Nanotechnology."
那是你的专长
That's your thing.
没错
Uh, yep.
那是我的专长
That's my thing.
但世界不能在过去修复 只有在未来才能
But the world's not fixed in the past, only the future.
未来与现在
The not yet. The now.
至少要有30 45公尺
Wow. Must be 100, 150 feet.
至少
Must be.
一张大圆桌
Big round table.
六张椅子 就在那里
Six chairs, right there.
但还能坐更多人
But room for more.
还能坐更多人
老天保佑我们
God help us.
现在就是你
The now is you.
什么
What?
这是刑事实验室最烂的工作
It's actually the worst job you can get in a crime lab.
不过我入门了
But, uh, my foot's in the door.
这是"真正"的工作
This is like a "job" job?
"真正的"
"Job" job.
你入门了
Your foot's in the door.
大家不都是这么说吗
Isn't that a thing people say?
你入门了
Your foot's in the door.
是啊 大家都是这么说
Yeah, that's something people say, man.
他入门了
-His foot's in the door!
-那是我的乖儿子 -噢 天啊
-That's my boy, right there! -Oh, gosh. Oh, gosh.
我什么都没教他
Taught him nothing he knows.
-爸 你会再被喷辣椒水 -好样的
-Yes! -Dad, you're gonna get maced again.
你的前途无量
No stopping you now.
谢了 爸
Thanks, Dad.
现在
Now.
现在是你崛起的时刻 维克多
Now's your time, Victor, to rise.
光是说声"谢谢你"并不够
"Thank you" is not enough for what you did.
我只是弥补一个错误而已
I just undid a mistake, that's all.
你怎么向银行把房子要回来的
How did you get the house back from the bank?
我买下了银行
I bought the bank.
对了 恭喜了
Congratulations, by the way.
坚持下去 勇往直前
Do this. Be this.
挚爱的父亲
塞拉斯·斯通 1969-2017
当一个我未曾当过的英雄
The man I never was. The hero you are.
在勇士之中占有一席之地
Take your place among the brave ones.
从前 现在与未来
The ones that were, that are, that are yet to be.
你该挺身而出了
It's time you stand,
勇敢奋战
fight,
努力发掘
discover,
愈合与爱
heal, love,
赢得胜利
win.
关键时刻…
The time
就是现在
is now.
准备好了吗
Ready?
来吧 史蒂芬
Come on, Stevens.
继续走吧
All right, let's keep it moving.
走吧
Keep going.
来吧 卢瑟 走吧
Come on, Luthor. Let's go.
卢瑟
Luthor.
打开二号牢房 卡尔
Open up two, Carl, please.
卢瑟
Luthor.
别闹了 卢瑟 不然我要进去教训你
All right, stop jerking around, Luthor, or I'm gonna have to come in there.
阿卡姆 哥谭市
阿卡姆精神病院
他来了
Ah, there he is.
欢迎上船
Welcome aboard.
来一杯顶级香槟
Care for a glass of Gout de Diamants?
我只是在庆祝神的回归
I was just celebrating God's return.
从地底回到天空
Out of the ground and back up into the sky.
听说你脑筋秀逗了
I heard you were a few clowns short of a circus.
本来是 谢谢你
I was, thank you,
直到阿卡汉的良医 让我的头脑再度清晰
until the good doctors at Arkham helped me find some much needed clarity.
你自愿免费干掉蝙蝠侠
Now, you volunteered to destroy the bat free of charge.
为什么这么好心
Why the pro bono work?
这是私人恩怨
It's personal.
让我猜 以眼还眼
Ah, let me guess, an eye for an eye?
你说你有我要的东西
You said you had something I'd want?
你最好别浪费我的时间
You'd better not be wasting my time.
我哪敢惹你呀 威尔森先生
Ooh. And endure your wrath, Mr. Wilson?
我有更重要的事要做 所以得好好活着
No, I wouldn't think of it. Uh, I have too much to live for. And more important things to do.
但如果你想找到蝙蝠侠
But if you want the Batman,
有件事可以帮你大忙
here is something that can help you.
他的名字是布鲁斯·韦恩
His name is Bruce Wayne.
现在想一想
Hmm. On second thought,
这件事的确值得庆祝
we do have something to celebrate.
好样的
Good boy.
安全
Clear.
还有多远
How much further?
就快到了
We're almost there.
我们得快点
Well, we need to hurry.
不能在外面待太久
We can't be out in the open much longer.
他会来找我们
He'll come for us.
让他来
Let him come.
让那个混蛋来吧
Let the bastard come.
他杀了亚瑟 我要一刀捅死他
I'll stab this through his heart for what he did to Arthur.
我要让他付出代价
I want to make him pay.
我知道你的感受 湄拉
I understand how you feel, Mera.
你一点都不知道
You have no idea how I feel.
但我们得按照计划才有机会成功
But we have to stick to the plan to have any chance to make this right.
你曾经爱过谁
Who have you ever loved?
你错了 小美人鱼
Au contraire, my little fish stick.
他很了解失去挚爱的感受
He knows exactly what it's like to lose someone he loves.
就像是…
You know, like, uh,
一个父亲
a father,
和一个母亲
like a mother.
你说下一句话前最好小心一点
Be very careful with the next thing you say.
或是一个养子
Like an adopted son.
对不对…
Isn't that right,
蝙蝠侠
Batman?
也许那只臭美人鱼是对的
Maybe, in a way, that smelly old flounder is right.
你对死亡麻木之前 还有多少人会死在你怀里
Because how many can die in your arms before you grow numb to death?
你说话一点都不小心
That's not very careful.
你还要看着多少死人的眼睛
And how many dead eyes can you look into
才会彻底心死
before you die inside yourself?
我已经心死了很久
I've been dead inside a long time,
但就连我也有忍耐极限
but even I have a limit.
你敢跨过那极限 我发誓会…
And if you cross that line, I swear to God, I will...
你会怎样 布鲁斯杀了我
Before what, Bruce? Kill me?
你不会杀我
You won't kill me.
我是你最好的朋友
I'm your best friend.
而且 谁会摸你的蛋蛋
Besides, who's gonna give you a reach-around?
反正呢
Anyway,
你需要我
you need me.
你…
You
让她死以后造成的这个世界 需要我帮你恢复原状
need me to help you undo this world you created by letting her die.
可怜的露易丝
Poor Lois.
她受尽了折磨
How she suffered so!
我常常在想
I often wonder
你在多少个平行时空毁灭世界 老实说…
how many alternate timelines do you destroy the world because...
都是因为你没种让自己死
frankly, you don't have the cojones to die yourself.
所以我还是一样比你更成熟
So, as usual, I'll be the bigger man.
停战吧
A truce,
布鲁斯
Bruce.
只要你有这张牌 我们就停战
As long as you have this card, a truce.
但你只要把它撕成一半 我就很乐意跟你谈谈
But all you have to do is tear it in half and I'm happy to discuss with you
你为什么要派那个神奇小子
in any way you like, why you sent the Boy Wonder
去做一个男人的工作
to do a man's job?
真的很好笑
You know, it's funny
你竟然敢说有多少人死在我怀里
that you would talk about people who died in my arms
当我把哈莉·奎茵抱在怀里
because when I held Harley Quinn
她满身是血 奄奄一息时
and she was bleeding and dying,
她用最后一口气哀求我
she begged me with her last breath
当我杀你的时候
that when I killed you,
别搞错 我一定会他妈的杀了你
and make no mistake, I will fucking kill you...
她要我慢慢来
that I'd do it slow.
我会信守这个承诺
I'm gonna honor that promise.
你真会演戏
Oh. You're good.
差点就唬住我了
You almost had me.
我们要躲在哪里
Where are we holing up?
他永远不会料到的地方
Somewhere he'll never suspect.
还是觉得带着他是个好主意吗
Still think it was a good idea bringing him along?
你觉得呢
-what do you think?
他找到我们了
He's found us.
我能帮你吗
Can I help you?
你一定知道达克赛德不会放过地球
I'm sure you know Darkseid is not finished with Earth.
反生命方程序就在这里
The Anti-Life Equation is here somewhere.
我们得赶在他之前找到它
We have to find it before he does.
决战时刻即将到来
There's a war coming.
我是来帮忙的
And I'm here to help.
抱歉 你是哪位
I'm sorry, who are you again?
我有很多名字和很多形体 就像你一样…
I've gone by many names and taken many forms. And like you,
我发现自己要对这世界负责
I've realized I have a stake in this world
我也该为它而战了
and it's time I started fighting for it.
我们是需要帮助
Well, we could definitely use the help.
所以很高兴你来了
So, glad you're here.
我没想过会看到地球的守护者
You know, I never thought I'd see the defenders of Earth
会团结一致 并肩作战
united and fighting as one.
没有你就不会发生 布鲁斯
It wouldn't have happened without you, Bruce.
你父母会为你感到骄傲
Your mother and father would be proud.
希望如此
I hope so.
我会保持联系
Well, I'll be in touch.
对了 有些人叫我…
Oh, and some have called me
火星猎人
the Martian Manhunter.
我猜我会再见到你
I guess I'll see you around.
献给秋